https://pci.edu/legal-terms-conditions/

Get More Info
AN ADMISSIONS REPRESENTATIVE WILL BE IN TOUCH WITH YOU SHORTLY.I need help with...
How do I enroll?
Information on Financial Aid.
When do classes start?
First Name*Last Name*Telephone*Email*
Program of Interest*Dental AssistantDiagnostic Medical SonographyMedical Assistant DiplomaRespiratory TherapySurgical TechnologyVeterinary TechnologyProspectIDNameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Legal Terms & Conditions
This Site and certain other web pages linked to this one (the “Site”) are owned and operated by Pittsburgh Career Institute (“Pittsburgh Career Institute”). The sections below contain the Legal Terms and Conditions covering the use of the Site. Additionally, you should review our Privacy Policy. Inquiries or concerns regarding this Legal Terms and Conditions or the Privacy Policy may be sent by any of the following: via e-mail to csmith@pci.edu or by mail to Privacy Matters, Pittsburgh Career Institute, 421 Seventh Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA  15219-1907.
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING LEGAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS (“OUR TERMS”) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO OUR TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT ASSENT TO OUR TERMS, YOU MAY NOT FURTHER ACCESS OR — USE THIS SITE.
RESTRICTIONS ON — USE OF MATERIALS
No materials from the Sites may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, re-deliver using framing technology, transmitted or distributed in any way without Pittsburgh Career Institute’s written permission; provided however, that users may download one copy of the materials on any single computer and print a copy of the materials for use in learning about, evaluating or acquiring Pittsburgh Career Institute and its programs. No other permission is granted. No permission is granted to use the Site’s icons, addresses or other means to hyperlink other web sites with any page in the Site. Prior written permission must be obtained from Pittsburgh Career Institute to hyperlink in any manner to the Site.
— USER REGISTRATION OR REQUEST FOR MORE INFORMATION
Some part(s) of the Site requires the user (“YOU”) to register in order to access certain features of the Site. In such a case, You will choose a user name and a password through the Site’s registration process. You are responsible for keeping Your user name and password confidential. You are responsible for all activities (whether by You or by others) that occur under your password and account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized uses of Your account or any other breach of security. Pittsburgh Career Institute cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to keep your account information protected.
Some parts of the Site offers the feature for You to submit contact information in order to receive additional information about the Pittsburgh Career Institute’s programs.
In either case, by affirmatively providing any personal information to through the Site, You assert that your information is true and accurate to the best of Your knowledge. You agree not to submit false information such as name, address, and or telephone number when affirmatively providing information through the Site. By providing information through the Site, You consent to receive periodic communication from Pittsburgh Career Institute, by e-mail. For more information on how Pittsburgh Career Institute may use the information You provide during registration, please see the .
Privacy Policy.
TRADEMARKS/COPYRIGHTS
The content of the Site, including all text and graphic images, is copyrighted by Pittsburgh Career Institute, its affiliates and/or the original copyright holder. The trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on the Site are registered or unregistered trademarks of Pittsburgh Career Institute, its affiliates or others. Nothing contained on the Site shall be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark or copyrightable material displayed without the written permission of or such other third party that may own the trademark or copyrightable material. You may not, without written permission, use any such marks or the “Pittsburgh Career Institute” name, including in any manner that disparages or discredits “Pittsburgh Career Institute.”
Copyright Complaints: Pittsburgh Career Institute respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement and is located on this Pittsburgh Career Institute website, please provide Pittsburgh Career Institute with the following information:
An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;
Description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;
The location of the material that you claim is infringing is located on this website;
Your address, telephone number and e-mail address;
A statement that your claim of infringement is based on a good faith belief; and
A statement made under penalty of perjury, that the information you have provided is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
Information and notice of claims of copyright infringement on its site should be referred to:
Attn:  Copyright Agent
Pittsburgh Career Institute
421 Seventh Avenue
Pittsburgh, PA  15219-1907
DISCLAIMER / LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
While Pittsburgh Career Institute uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up to date information on the Site, Pittsburgh Career Institute makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. Pittsburgh Career Institute assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of the Site.
Certain linked web sites are not under the control of Pittsburgh Career Institute, and Pittsburgh Career Institute is not responsible for the content of any third party linked site, or of any other links contained in such third party site. Pittsburgh Career Institute provides links for your convenience only, and the inclusion of any link is not an endorsement by Pittsburgh Career Institute of the site or its contents.
THE MATERIALS ON, OR ACCESSIBLE FROM, THE SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. PITTSBURGH CAREER INSTITUTE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER(S) THAT MAKE THE SITE AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. PITTSBURGH CAREER INSTITUTE DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE — USE, OR THE RESULTS OF THE — USE OF THE MATERIALS ON, OR ACCESSED THROUGH, THE SITES IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
IN NO EVENT WILL PITTSBURGH CAREER INSTITUTE BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES RESULTING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITES, THEIR CONTENT, OR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THEIR TECHNICAL OPERATION OR CONTENT, EVEN IF PITTSBURGH CAREER INSTITUTE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
By using the Site, You agree to indemnify, hold harmless and defend Pittsburgh Career Institute from any claims, damages, losses, liabilities, and all costs and expenses of defense, including but not limited to attorneys’ fees, resulting directly or indirectly from a claim by a third party that is based on your use of the Site in violation of Our Terms.
CHANGES TO WEB SITE AND/OR OUR TERMS
Pittsburgh Career Institute reserves the right to alter or delete material from the Site at any time and may, at any time and in its sole discretion, revise and/or update these Terms. You are bound by any such revision and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the these Terms.
OTHER PROVISIONS
Our Terms shall be governed by, and construed and enforced in accordance with, the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, without regard to its conflicts of law principles. If any provision of Our Terms shall be unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from Our Terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any the remaining parts of Our Terms. Our Terms represent the entire agreement between Pittsburgh Career Institute and You relating to the subject matter contained herein. No delay or failure by Pittsburgh Career Institute to take action under Our Terms will constitute a waiver of any of the provisions contained herein, or rights provided hereby, unless expressly waived in writing by Pittsburgh Career Institute. No single waiver will constitute a continuing or subsequent waiver.
View
Oct 30
Open
View
Oct 28
Open
View
Oct 27
Privacy Statement (FERPA)
421 Seventh Ave.
Pittsburgh, PA 15219
Site by Oozle Media © 2020 Pittsburgh Career Institute
